No, I have to finish my hair. Come here. I have to finish my hair, babush.
Guess who's coming back to radio? Guess who's coming back to radio? I said, guess who's coming
back to radio? It's me. It's me. It's me. Guess who's coming back to radio? Who? Guess who's
coming back to radio? What? Guess who's coming back to radio? It's me. It's me. It's me.
They can't keep a good one dong. Always keep a smile when they want me. Goddamn. Goddamn.
So I will be joining Tavis Smiley's KBLA Talk 1580 starting next Friday, the 17th, with
a weekly show all summer. It's going to be a sealed summer. And you can listen to the
show by downloading the KBLA Talk 1580 app. That is going to be the only way you can hear
my show. And I will be on live. I will be I'll be on 12 to two and four to six. So I just
want to shout out Tavis because he was really like, do what you want to do. Do what you want
to do. So really, really appreciate the brethren coming through and being like, yo, I respect
you. I respect your voice. And we got a space in place for it. So looking forward to that.
And it's KBLA Talk 1580. I will be promoting this a lot. So if you miss it here right now,
you're going to get it again. And you know, I'm not going to be telling the news like that's
not the point. There's enough people telling the news. We got to be talking about other
things more than the news because we got to talk about what is going on that's creating
this type of news. You heard me? That's where I come in. And so I'm so happy to bring that.
Of course, thank you, Joe, to bring that to a black owned space with someone who consistently
makes spaces for black voices and supports black community. So it's not enough to be black owned.
It's how do you live as a black person through what you own? You heard me? So I don't know
where that you heard me came from. I just got, I just got New Orleans-ian real quick. I was
listening to Master P yesterday. So if you want to show me some love and you want to show them some
love for bringing me over there, make sure you download the KBLA Talk 1580 app. Download,
all right, download the KBLA Talk 1580 and 1580 app. And when you download that app, like they're
going to be like seeing that these are people who are in support of Amanda. So Logan, that's some
bullshit. So I start next Friday, the 17th and I'm looking forward to it. Looking forward to,
you know, continuing my journey as a voice for change, for elevation. Thank you, Daffy C86 for
downloading. Thank you, Mars Ross for downloading. Thank you, Katara Faith for downloading. Thank you,
Ycard underscore six for downloading. You know, it's thank you, BB72EC for downloading. You know,
this is, this is a business and this is, Mando is right there. Mando is right there. This is a
business and an industry that will continually try to convince you that you're not the dopeness that you
are. Stay the course, refine, believe in yourself. Never stop. Never stop. Thank you, goddess love,
all I said, Beverly. Never stop. Even when it looks like, damn, I'm not doing what I was doing before.
Keep the momentum going. There's peaks and valleys. You feel me? So keep the momentum going. Thank you,
safari underscore el. Thank you, CDN three. Thank you, key to gem. So for those of y'all who are just
joining, I am starting a radio show again. It's happening starting next Friday. We got a seal
summer going down at Tavis Smiley's talk radio. Uh, he has a talk radio network that's based in
Leimert Park, LA. It's called KBLA talk 1580. And I will be on Fridays, 12 to two and four to six.
And you can listen to the show by downloading the KBLA talk 1580 app. And when you download that app,
you're showing them that they did the right thing by bringing me on the show or bringing me on the
network. So tell your friends and, um, tune in. I will be promoting it of course. And again, I just
want to shout out Tavis for just always actually being a supporter of my voice. Um, and you know,
now getting behind it by platforming it for, you know, a consistent amount of time. Thank you, BB. Okay.
Man, listen, stay the course y'all. Stay the gosh darn course. I'm gonna go eat my dinner.
Bye. I'll see y'all in Harlem tomorrow night. If you didn't get your tickets to Radical Rhythm
Experience tomorrow night, you can get them online and you can get them at the door and everyone who
comes to the show will get a free Malcolm X notebook. No, I'm crocheting. And if you can't
come to Harlem, then baby you can watch online because I will be streaming it on YouTube, Amanda
Seals TV. The link is in the video. I mean, sorry, the link is in the bio and you can go to YouTube
and, um, sign up for notifications because the link is already live. All right. Thank y'all for
all the support in the work I'm doing. Appreciate you.